<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_changelog">Changelog</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_get_started">Get started</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_skip">Skip</string>

  <string name="feature_onboarding_welcome_page_title">Welcome to ScenePeek</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_welcome_page_description">A free and open-source client for TMDB &amp; Jellyseerr</string>

  <string name="feature_onboarding_whats_new_title">What's new in %1$s for %2$s</string>

  <string name="feature_onboarding_tmdb_page_title">TMDB</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_tmdb_page_description">Connect your TMDB account to access your watchlist, ratings, lists and more.</string>

  <string name="feature_onboarding_jellyseerr_page_title">Jellyseerr</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_jellyseerr_page_description">Connect to your Jellyseerr instance to request movies and TV shows instantly.</string>

  <string name="feature_onboarding_link_handling_page_title">IMDb &amp; TMDB Link Handling</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_link_handling_page_description"><![CDATA[ScenePeek can open <strong>URLs</strong> from <strong>IMDb</strong> & <strong>TMDB</strong> in the app. This can be useful for opening links to movies, TV shows and people directly in the app.]]></string>

  <string name="feature_onboarding_v29_grid_view">- Allow user to switch between grid and list view on media lists</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v29_discover_rating_filter">- Add new discover filters. You can now also discover movies and tv shows by filtering with ratings and minimum votes.</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v29_favorite_status_lists">- Display media favorite status on list details</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v29_discover_filters">- Fix an issue with discover filters between movies and tv shows</string>

  <string name="feature_onboarding_v30_convert_app_to_multiplatform">- Huge updates to ScenePeek codebase. An iOS version will soon be released!</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v30_display_fullscreen_posters">- View posters in full screen for movies, TV shows, and people. Click any poster on a details screen to expand it to full screen!</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v30_external_ratings">- Add Rotten Tomatoes and Metacritic scores</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v30_fix_jellyfin_auth_with_empty_passwords">- Enable login for Jellyfin/Emby users with empty passwords</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v30_fix_encryption">- Migrate deprecated encryption library. If you were previously connected on TMDB, you'll need to re-login.</string>

  <string name="feature_onboarding_v32_improve_search">- Improve search functionality. You can now get categorized results for movies, tv shows, people, or just search through all!</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v32_show_year_on_search">- Show media release year on search and discover results</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v32_add_custom_color_option"><![CDATA[- Added a custom color theme option! Head to <strong>Settings > Appearance</strong> to give the app a more personal touch]]></string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v32_add_detailed_error_messages_for_seerr">- Add detailed error messages on jellyseerr login</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v32_add_detailed_csrf_warning">- Add detailed warning when CSRF is enabled on user's jellyseerr instance</string>

  <string name="feature_onboarding_v33_redesign_home_screen">- Redesign home screen. Add sections to easily find trending, popular, upcoming and top rated movies and tv shows.</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v33_update_favorites">- Favorites are now categorized to movies and tv shows</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v33_fix_duplicate_ids_crash">- Fixed an issue where the app crashed due to invalid movie cast data</string>

  <string name="feature_onboarding_v34_add_discover_year_filter">- Discover now includes year filtering. Find movies by year, decade, or year range</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v34_add_discover_sorting_option">- Discover now includes sorting options. Sort by year, ratings, revenue, and more</string>
  <string name="feature_onboarding_v34_user_data_empty_state">- Redesigned empty state visuals for watchlist, ratings, and empty lists</string>

  <string name="feature_onboarding_v35_add_email_support_field">- Add experimental warning and email support field on Jellyseerr login</string>

  <string name="v36_season_and_episode_details_screen">- Introducing new season &amp; episode details screen! You can now view information about each season and episode, and if you're logged into to TMDB, you can also rate individual episodes.</string>

  <string name="v37_movies_collection">- Introduce collections screen! Show if movie belongs to a collection and lists all the movies included in that collection</string>
  <string name="v37_discover_by_keyword">- Discover now also include the keyword filter</string>
  <string name="v37_detail_keywords">- Show keywords on a movie or TV show information that describe its plot or mood</string>
  <string name="v37_clickable_genres_and_keywords">- Genres and keywords are now clickable, taking you to Discover with the corresponding filter applied</string>
</resources>